Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Publications and Ephemera MC.334
New York University Archives
- RG 27.0. Stern School of Business, the Undergraduate College, 1901-2021
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1932-1938, 1962-1963, 2006-2011 (Box 165, Folder 12)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1932-1933, 1974-1988 (Box 195, Folder 14, Box 167, Folder 11)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Press Clippings Scrapbook, 1922-1937 (Box 257)
- RG 27.1. 50th Anniversary, 1950
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1950 (Box 263, Folder 5-7)
- RG 27.5. Department of Marketing, 2021
  - Stern Marketing 2020-2021 Newsletter, August 2021
    Annual publication of Stern's Marketing Department. It contains accomplishments of the department's faculty, students, and alumni and provide updates on activities and events.
  - Stern Marketing Newsletter, May 2021
- RG 28.0. Stern School of Business, the Graduate Division, 1919-2019
  - Executive MBA Blog, April 2014-April 2019
    Executive MBA Blog features articles from students from the Executive MBA program at Stern. The blog dates back to 2009 and features articles on work-life-school balance, Arrowwood residency, Stern clubs, teamwork, Global Study Tour, Berkley Center business plan competition, entrepreneurship, advice for being in the program, curriculum, and other highlights from the program.
  - The GBA Newsletter, 1969-1979 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - GBA Update, 1988 (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - I.N.E. Reports, 1985 (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Leonard N. Stern School of Business Executive MBA Program Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for the Executive MBA Program at New York University's Stern School of Business. The page focuses on the Entrepreneur's Challenge, admissions, alumni news, Global Study Tour, Arrowwood residency, student profiles, and other events.
  - Leonard N. Stern School of Business Executive MBA Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed for the Executive MBA Program at New York University's Stern School of Business. Tweets include student profiles, speakers series, Global Study Tour, information sessions, conference notices, and other event listings.
  - New York University Bulletin, 1957 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - NYU Business, 1982-1990 (Box 264, Folder 5-10, Box 265, Folder 1-2)
  - Stern Executive Education Programs Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed for the Stern Executive Education Programs. Tweet topics include course listing; professors Aswath Damodaran, Ed Altman, Viral Acharya, Anindya Ghose, and other professors' work; conferences; investment decision making; risk management; valuation; leadership training; and other articles.
  - Stern Business, 1999-2002 (Box 265, Folder 3-4)
  - Stern Business Report, 1990 (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1919-1982 (Box 265, Folder 6-10, Box 266, Folder 1-7, Box 267, Folder 1-5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1981-2012 (Box 268, Folder 1-6, Box 269)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1978-1986, undated (Box 195, Folder 15)
- RG 28.1. Salomon Brothers Center for the Study of Financial Institutions, 1952-1983
  - Current Business Studies, 1952 (Box 269, Folder 7)
  - Monograph Series in Finance and Economics, 1978-1981 (Box 269, Folder 8, Box 270, Folder 1, Box 271, Item 1-2)
  - Newsletter, 1975-1983 (Box 270, Folder 1)
  - Occasional Papers in Metropolitan Business and Finance, 1979-1980 (Box 270, Folder 3-4)
  - Working Paper Series, 1981 (Box 270, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1971-1982 (Box 270, Folder 6-8)
- RG 28.4. Ross Institute for Accounting Research, 1978-1982
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1978-1982 (Box 278, Folder 1)
- RG 28.5. Office of Career Development, 1987-1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1987-1988 (Box 278, Folder 2)
- RG 28.6. Office of the Dean, 1990
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1990 (Box 278, Folder 3)
- RG 28.7. Center for Japan / U.S. Business and Economic Studies, 1985-1999
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1985-1999 (Box 278, Folder 4)
- RG 28.8. C.J. Devine Institute of Finance, 1959-1976
  - The Bulletin of C.J. Devine Institute of Finance, 1959-1966 (Box 272, Folder 1-4, Box 273, Box 274)
  - The Bulletin of C.J. Devine Institute of Finance, 1965-1971 (Box 275, Folder 1-3, Box 276, Folder 1-4, Box 277)
  - The Bulletin of C.J. Devine Institute of Finance, 1975-1976 (Box 278, Folder 5-6)
- RG 29.0. Faculty of Business Administration (FBA) / School of Business, 1963-2000
  - Reprint Series, 1963-1968 (Box 279, Folder 1-2, Box 280, Folder 1-5, Box 281, Folder 1-4)
  - Reprint Series, 1969-1970 (Box 282, Folder 1-5)
  - Schools of Business Newsletter, 1974-1977 (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - Weekly Digest of News and Views, 1975-1988 (Box 283, Folder 2-4)
  - Working Paper Series, 1974-1981 (Box 283, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1965-2000 (Box 283, Folder 6-7)
- RG 29.1. Computer Application Information Systems Area (Center for Research on Information Systems, CRIS), 1980-1981
  - Center for Research on Information Systems Pamphlet, 1980-1981 (Box Shared University Archives 149, Folder 3)
- RG 29.2. Institute of International Finance, 1926-1958
  - Institute of International Finance Bulletin, 1926-1935 (Box 283, Folder 8-9, Box 284, Folder 1-3, Box 285, Folder 1-4)
  - Institute of International Finance Bulletin, 1936-1946 (Box 286, Folder 1-5, Box 287, Box 288, Folder 1-6)
  - Institute of International Finance Bulletin, 1947-1958 (Box 289, Folder 1-6, Box 290, Box 278, Folder 7-8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1927-1938 (Box 278, Folder Unknown)
- RG 31.0. College of / School of Architecture and Allied Science, 1924-1941
  - The Bulletin of the Beaux-Arts Institute of Design, August-September 1934 (Box 291, Folder 1-2)
  - The Bulletin of the Work of the Graduate Students in the School of Architecture and Allied Arts, 1937-1940 (Box 291, Folder 3-5)
  - The Column, 1931 (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - The Podium, 1937-1938, 1941 (Box 291, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1924-1941 (Box 291, Folder 7-8, Box 292, Folder 1-4)
- RG 32.0. School of Professional Studies (SCPS), 1924-2020
  - Adult-Study Catalogue, 1936-1938 (Box 292, Folder 5)
  - Adult-Study Guide, 1936-1943 (Box 292, Folder 6-7, Box 293, Folder 1-2)
  - Adult-Study Outlines, 1936-1938 (Box 293, Folder 3)
  - Bulletins of Emergency Adult Education Program in New York, 1936 (Box 294, Folder 1)
  - Career Trend Letter, 1989 (Box 293, Folder 4)
  - Changing Scene, 1992, 1995, 1997 (Box 293, Folder 5, Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Continuing Education, 1966-1975 (Box 293, Folder 6-8, Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Continuing Education News, 1976-1985 (Box 293, Folder 9)
  - Corporate Review, 1990, 1996 (Box 294, Folder 2)
  - Courses for Adults, 1952 (Box 294, Folder 3)
  - DDS Newsletter, 1981 (Box 294, Folder 4)
  - Icarus, 1984-1998 (Box 294, Folder 5-8, Box 295, Folder 1-5)
  - New York University Bulletin, 1952, 1967 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  - Night and Day, Autumn 1984 (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - NYU Schack Institute of Real Estate Newsletter, 2009 (Box 296, Folder 2)
  - Portraits, 1984-2000 (Box 296, Folder 3-5)
  - School of Continuing Education Newsletter, 1978-1983 (Box 296, Folder 6)
  - School of Continuing and Professional Studies Facebook, May-September 2014
    NYU-SCPS Facebook page. Facebook captures from 2014 do not playback.
  - School of Continuing and Professional Studies Twitter, May-September 2014
    Twitter page of the NYU School of Continuing and Professional Studies. Tweet topics include the Art Crime Symposium, Sports and Society Conference on Bullying, NYU Publishing, PRISM, and other events.
  - School of Professional Studies Newsletter Archive, May 2020
    NYU School of Professional Studies newsletters for faculty and students.
  - School of Professional Studies Newsletter Archive, April 2014-April 2019
    PDFs of the School of Professional Studies newsletters. The website contains three publications: the NYU School of Professional Studies News (2009-2018), Faculty News (2014-2018), and Student News (2014-2018).
  - School of Professional Studies Twitter, September 2014-May 2015
    Twitter page of the NYU School of Professional Studies. Tweets are related to admissions, symposia, career development, Schack Institute of Real Estate, student government, conferences, the NYU Heyman Center, graduation, the name change of the school, alumni, networking, Tisch Center, Tisch Institute for Global Sport, and other events and news.
  - SCPS News, 2011, 2013 (Box 296, Folder 7)
  - Working Knowledge, 1999 (Box 296, Folder 8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1924-1989 (Box 296, Folder 9-11, Box 297, Folder 1-7, Box 298, Folder 1-8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1980-2003 (Box 322, Folder 3-4, Box 165, Folder 13-15)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1989-2013 (Box 299, Folder 1-6, Box 300, Box 301, Folder 1-4)
- RG 32.1. American Language Institute, 1965-1991
  - The American Language Institute Bulletin, 1974-1975 (Box 301, Folder 5)
  - Occasional Papers, 1965 (Box 301, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1965-1991 (Box 301, Folder 7-10, Box 302, Folder 1-2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1965-2003 (Box 322, Folder 5)
- RG 32.3. The Real Estate Institute, 1969-2006, 2021-ongoing
  - New York University Bulletin, 1969-1975 (Box 302, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint, August 2021-ongoing
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1972-2006 (Box 302, Folder 4-8, Box 303, Folder 1-7, Box 304, Folder 1-4)
- RG 32.4. Center for Safety Education, 1937-1975
  - Driver Education, 1957 (Box 304, Folder 5)
  - Family Recreation, 1961 (Box 304, Folder 6)
  - Ground Safety in Aviation Operations, 1954 (Box 304, Folder 7)
  - The Human Element in Industrial Accident Prevention, 1955 (Box 304, Folder 8)
  - The Safety Training Digest, 1943 (Box 304, Folder 9)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1937-1975 (Box 305, Folder 1)
- RG 32.5. The Reading Institute, 1952-1976
  - New York University Bulletin -- The Reading Institute, 1965-1970 (Box 305, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1952-1976 (Box 305, Folder 3-4)
- RG 32.6. The Management Institute (changed to Marketing and Management Institute), 1950-1990
  - New York University Bulletin -- The Management Institute, 1965-1972 (Box 305, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1950-1990 (Box 305, Folder 6-8, Box 306, Folder 1-4)
- RG 32.7. The Mortgage Institute, 1975-1984
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1975-1984 (Box 306, Folder 5)
- RG 32.8. The Institute on Federal Taxation / Institute on Taxation / Institute of Finance, Law and Taxation, 1943-2004
  - Coordinators' Cyclopedic Tax Service, 1943 (Box 306, Folder 6)
  - New York University Bulletin -- School of Continuing Education, 1973 (Box 306, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1953-2004 (Box 306, Folder 8-9, Box 307, Folder 1-7, Box 308, Folder 1)
- RG 32.9. The Institute of Paralegal Studies, 1977-2004
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1977-2004 (Box 308, Folder 2-4)
- RG 32.10. Information Technologies Institute, 1970-2004
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1970-2004 (Box 308, Folder 5-7, Box 309, Folder 1-6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 2001-2003 (Box 322, Folder 6)
- RG 32.11. Center for Publishing, 1957-2004
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1957-2004 (Box 310, Folder 1-6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1984-2003 (Box 322, Folder 7)
- RG 32.12. Paul McGhee Division, 1964-1998
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1964-1998 (Box 310, Folder 7, Box 311, Folder 1-5)
- RG 32.13. General Studies Program, 1970-2008
  - New York University Bulletin -- General Studies Program, 2006-2007 (Box 311, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1970s-1980s, 1993-2008 (Box 311, Folder 7-8, Box 312, Folder 1-2)
- RG 32.14. Division of Arts, Sciences, and Humanities, 1965-2003
  - The West 4th St Review, 1996-1997 (Box 312, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1965, 1985-2003 (Box 312, Folder 4-6)
- RG 32.15. Division of Professional and Industry Programs, 1964-2004
  - New York University Bulletin -- Continuing Professional Education in Business and Management, 1970-1971 (Box 312, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1964-2004 (Box 312, Folder 8, Box 313, Folder 1-5)
- RG 32.16. Appraisal Studies Program, 1986-2004
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1986-2004 (Box 313, Folder 6, Box 314, Folder 1-2)
- RG 32.17. Office of Public Affairs and Student Services, 1991-2000
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1991-2000 (Box 314, Folder 3-4)
- RG 32.18. Center for Career and Life Planning, 1968
  - New York University Bulletin -- School of Continuing Education and Extension Services, 1968 (Box 314, Folder 5)
- RG 32.19. Program in Film, Video and Broadcasting, 1982-2004
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1982-2004 (Box 314, Folder 6-7, Box 315, Folder 1)
- RG 32.20. Center for Direct Marketing, 1957-2002
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1957-2002 (Box 315, Folder 2-5)
- RG 32.21. Corporate Education Service, 1963-2003
  - Corporate Preview, 1991 (Box 315, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1963-2003 (Box 315, Folder 7)
- RG 32.22. Environmental Management, 1991-1995
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1991-1995 (Box 316, Folder 1)
- RG 32.23. The Center for Hospitality, Tourism, and Travel Administration, 1979-2012
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1979-2012 (Box 316, Folder 2-7, Box 317, Folder 1-5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1998-2004 (Box 322, Folder 8)
- RG 32.24. Foreign Language Program / Department, 1956-2004
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1956-2004 (Box 317, Folder 6, Box 318, Folder 1-4)
- RG 32.25. International Programs, 1976-2000
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1976-2000 (Box 318, Folder 5-6)
- RG 32.26. Health Related Programs, 1980-1998
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1980-1998 (Box 318, Folder 7-8)
- RG 32.27. Writing / Speech Programs, 1975-1987
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1975-1997 (Box 318, Folder 9, Box 319, Folder 1)
- RG 32.28. Public Housing Management Program, 1938
  - Public Housing Management, 1938 (Box 319, Folder 2)
- RG 32.29. Formerly Paul McGhee Division, 1998-2008
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1998-2008 (Box 319, Folder 3-5)
- RG 32.30. Non-Governmental Organizations, 2000
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2000 (Box 319, Folder 6)
- RG 32.31. Center for Philanthropy and Fundraising, 1999-2006
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1999-2006 (Box 320, Folder 1-2)
- RG 32.32. Virtual College, 1999-2004
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1999-2004 (Box 320, Folder 3-4)
- RG 32.33. The Institute on Family Wealth, 2000
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2000 (Box 320, Folder 5)
- RG 32.34. Communications Technologies, 2001
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2001 (Box 320, Folder 6)
- RG 32.36. Center for Instructional Design and Online Education, 2002-2003
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2002-2003 (Box 320, Folder 7)
- RG 32.37. Midtown Center, 1979-1997
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1979-1997 (Box 320, Folder 8)
- RG 32.38. Center for Global Affairs, 2005-2014
  - Perspectives on Global Issues, 2014 (Box 320, Folder 9)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2005-2006 (Box 320, Folder 10)
- RG 32.39. Creative Arts Team, 1981-1990
  - CAT Tales, 1990 (Box 320, Folder 11)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1981-1986 (Box 320, Folder 12)
- RG 33.0. Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service, 1949-2018, undated
  - GPA News Notes, 1950-1968 (Box 321, Folder 1-3)
  - GPA Newsletter, 1977-1988 (Box 321, Folder 4-6)
  - GPA Quarterly, 1982-1983 (Box 321, Folder 7)
  - GPA Review, 1979 (Box 321, Folder 8)
  - GPA-SA Newsletter, 1984 (Box 321, Folder 9)
  - The Graduate Health Student Newsletter, 1980 (Box 321, Folder 10)
  - NYU Wagner Doctoral Program Update, 2008-2009 (Box 321, Folder 11)
  - Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service Facebook, May 2014-November 2018
    Facebook page for the Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service. The page includes posts on articles by Wagner alumni, the Rudin Center, awards, commencement, book reviews, public service, and events.
  - Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed for the Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service. Tweet topics include alumni news, news from the Rudin Center and the Furman Center, nonprofit job opportunities, Wagner's 75th anniversary, commencement, Day of Service, service awards, fellowships, and links to articles.
  - Robert F. Wagner School of Public Service Alumni e-News, July-August 2014
    Newsletter for the alumni of the Wagner School of Public Service. It includes messages from the Dean, lectures, regional events, and other news. The newsletter dates back to October 2004.
  - The Student/Alumni-ae Placement Newsletter, 1985-1986 (Box 321, Folder 12-14, Box 323, Folder 1-3)
  - Wagner Update, 1996 (Box 323, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1949-2006, undated (Box 323, Folder 5-9, Box 324, Folder 1-3)
- RG 33.1. Institute of Labor Relations, 1964-1984
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1964-1984 (Box 324, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1981-1982, 2000-2001 (Box 343, Folder 1)
- RG 33.3. Urban Research Center, 1983-1995
  - New York Affairs, 1983 (Box 324, Folder 5)
  - Reinventing New York, 1991 (Box 324, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1986-1995 (Box 324, Folder 7)
- RG 33.4. Center for Science and Technology, 1979-1981
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1979-1981 (Box 325, Folder 1-2)
- RG 33.5. John Brademas Center for the Study of Congress, 2005-2022
  - John Brademas Center Publications, May 2022-ongoing
    Reports and publications from the John Brademas Center that works to develop a greater understanding of the United States Congress. Publications focus not only on examining the rules and procedures of Congress but also the ways in which the Senate and House of Representatives help determine the substance of law and policy for the Government of the United States – through their leaders, committees, caucuses, conferences, staffs and individual members, and through the interaction of Congress with the executive and judicial branches. Publications also focus on public opinion about Congress.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2005-2009 (Box 325, Folder 3)
- RG 33.6. Rudin Center for Transportation Policy and Management, 2014-2019
  The Rudin Center for Transportation Policy and Management explores current and emerging challenges in transportation and infrastructure.
  - Rudin Center for Transportation Policy and Management Blog, April 2014-November 2019
    The website contains information on their staff and faculty, events, press, publications, and blog. The blog shifted to the homepage of the Rudin Center in 2014. The blog's areas of focus include infrastructure, paratransit, transportation planning and policy, bikes, technology and smart cities, aviation, urban mobility, economic development, and New York City.
  - Rudin Center for Transportation Policy and Management Blog, May 2014
    Blog for the Rudin Center for Transportation Policy and Management, with posts dating back to August 2011. The blog focuses on news related to transportation and infrastructure, opinion pieces on transportation policy, public transit and driving analysis with a focus on New York City and the surrounding areas, transportation and commuter statistics, event announcements and recaps, social media and transportation, images of transportation and Rudin Center events, how major events affected transportation (Hurricane Sandy and September 11), and innovation in transportation.
  - The Mobility Factbook, May 2014-November 2019
    This website is a New York City mobility and transportation fact book assembled by New York University's Rudin Center for Transportation Policy and Management which celebrates NYC's transportation diversity and features fact sheets about common modes of transportation including public and commercial air, water, rail, and road transportation as well as private road and water transportation. These fact sheets feature photos, infographics and statistical information about their prevalence over the last several years, and (nonfunctional) social media feeds which populate with topical content related to each mode of transportation. The home page warns that the Factbook is a work in progress and advises users to check back for updates, but the site has not received any major updates since at least 2014 when New York University web crawling of the site began. The site was likely abandoned during development.
- RG 33.7. Stephen Charney Vladeck Junior Faculty Fellowship, 2006-2007
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2006-2007 (Box 325, Folder 4)
- RG 33.9. Organizational Performance Initiative, 2014-2018
  The Organizational Performance Initiative (OPI) is designed to help organizations respond to the increased uncertainty that surrounds their missions.
  - Organizational Performance Initiative News, May 2014-May 2018
    The initiative focuses on helping all organizations all sectors of the economy: government, charitable and business. It also focuses on helping learning institutions such as colleges and universities, standards-setting agencies, Congress, and the presidency improve their policies on behalf of greater preparedness for the many futures ahead. The news page contains 2011-2013 event descriptions involving Paul C. Light, the founding principal investigator for OPI.
- RG 34.0. Silver School of Social Work (SSW), 1964-2021
  - Center for the Study of Unemployed Youth -- Training Series Booklets, 1965-1966 (Box 325, Folder 5-6)
  - Graduate School of Social Work Newsletter, 1969-1979 (Box 325, Folder 7)
  - Journal of Current Social Work Thought, 1968-1969 (Box 325, Folder 8)
  - Manpower Training Series, 1968 (Box 325, Folder 9)
  - New York University Bulletin -- Shirley M. Ehrenkranz School of Social Work, 2000 (Box 326, Folder 1)
  - NYU Social Work, 2003-2007 (Box 326, Folder 2)
  - News Brief, 1990-1997, undated (Box 326, Folder 3)
  - News Brief for Friends of the School, 1989-1990 (Box 326, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings of the International Social Work Conference, 1998 (Box 326, Folder 5)
  - Silver School of Social Work Student Affairs Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for the student affairs at NYU Silver School of Social Work. Facebook posts include fellowship awards, mental health and race, student group leadership, professional development, photos from events, job listings, integrated health, research opportunities, sexual assault awareness, poverty in higher education, student awards, networking, stress relief, mindfulness, and other events.
  - Silver School of Social Work Summer 2020 Scholarship & Impact Newsletter, May 2021
    The summer issue of Scholarship & Impact focuses on alumni and student news, faculty awards and honors, grant announcements, and faculty in the news
  - Silver School of Social Work Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    News and updates for the NYU Silver School of Social Work community. Tweet topics include professional development, lectures, loan forgiveness, poverty, housing precarity, and the LGBTQIA+ community.
  - Social Work, 2008-2014 (Box 326, Folder 6-8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1964-2012 (Box 326, Folder 9, Box 327, Folder 1-8, Box 328)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1980-1982, 2003-2009 (Box 343, Folder 2)
- RG 34.3. Center on Violence and Recovery, 2014-2015
  - Center on Violence and Recovery Facebook, May 2014-August 2015